var title = 'Traduza para grego.<br>Para substantivos, inclua o artigo definido (ο, η, το...).';

var questions = [

 {
   prompt: "o Acrópolis",
   answer: ["η Ακρόπολη", "η ακρόπολη", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "a farmácia",
   answer: ["το φαρμακείο", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "o mar",
   answer: ["η θάλασσα", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "o correio",
   answer: ["το ταχυδρομείο", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "o hotel",
   answer: ["το ξενοδοχείο", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "a lavanderia",
   answer: ["το καθαριστήριο", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "o bar",
   answer: ["το μπαρ", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "a discoteca",
   answer: ["η ντίσκο", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "o Pangrati (bairro)",
   answer: ["το Παγκράτι", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "o caixa (para pagar)",
   answer: ["το ταμείο", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "a montanha",
   answer: ["το βουνό", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "o museu",
   answer: ["το μουσείο", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "o prédio",
   answer: ["η πολυκατοικία", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "o Plaka (bairro)",
   answer: ["η Πλάκα", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "a Creta",
   answer: ["η Κρήτη", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "a Grécia",
   answer: ["η Ελλάδα", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "a Europa",
   answer: ["η Ευρώπη", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "o Brachami (bairro)",
   answer: ["το Μπραχάμι", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "o Sunião (cabo de Atenas)",
   answer: ["το Σούνιο", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

];